repairclinic.com 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy - RepairClinic.com

This Privacy Policy sets out the manner in which RepairClinic.com, Inc. (“RepairClinic.com”) collects, uses, discloses and otherwise manages the personal information of our customers. 

## Your acceptance of our privacy policy

By using the web site http://www.repairclinic.com (the “Site”), you agree to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this policy. If we make any significant changes to this policy, we will notify you by email, or post a notice of such changes on the Site, or flag our Privacy Policy on the Site as updated. 

## What personal information we collect and how we use it

**Purchases:** When you purchase a product we may collect your shipping and billing address, payment information, phone number and email address. If you leave items in your shopping cart prior to completing a purchase on our Site, we may email you reminders about those items left in your shopping cart. If you choose to create an account on our Site, we will also collect a user name and password. We use this information to administer your account and process your order and any returns. 

**Promotional Emails:** From time to time we may obtain your consent to send you our promotional emails containing information about RepairClinic.com products and services. You can unsubscribe from our email list at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link in any of our email messages or by contacting us as set out below. 

**Contests:** When you enter a contest, sweepstakes or participate in a promotion, we may collect your name, address, phone number, email address, and other information you provide. We use this information to administer your participation in the contest, sweepstakes or promotion. 

**Surveys:** From time to time, we may offer you the opportunity to participate in one of our surveys or other customer research. The information obtained through our surveys and customer research is used in an aggregated, non-personally identifiable form. We use this information to help us understand our customers, and to enhance our product and service offerings, promotions and events. 

**Contact Us:** We also collect information when you contact us with a question, comment or complaint, including when you use our Live Chat program. For example, we may collect your name, email address and any additional information we need to help us respond to your question or comment (such as your order number or any product information). We may retain this information to assist you in the future and to improve our customer service, product and service offerings. 

## How we protect your personal information

We have implemented technical, physical and administrative safeguards designed to protect personal information against loss, theft or unauthorized or unlawful access, use, disclosure, alteration or destruction. 

All passwords are stored on our server in encrypted form. If you lose your password, we will generate a new one and send it to you. 

We have personal information retention processes designed to retain personal information for no longer than necessary for the purposes stated above or to otherwise meet legal requirements. 

## Other data we collect that is not personally identifiable

We collect information regarding your use of the Site, such as computer-related information (browser type you used, your Internet Protocol address, last URL visited, and the date and time of day of your login). We send a “cookie” or “pixel tag” to your computer which contains an identification number that is unique to the computer you are using. You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result, and some services may not be available. We use this information to enhance the experience of using the Site, to tailor our Site for you and other future visitors, to understand how our Site is used, to investigate and verify proper conduct at the Site, and to monitor the security and integrity of the Site. 

We may also use third parties to serve our advertisements on other websites. These companies may use tracer tags or web beacons to report certain information (but not your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to our Site and the websites which advertise and feature links to our Site, in order to measure the effectiveness of our advertisements. 

We use data in the aggregate for our business purposes, but we do not use it in a manner that allows identification of an individual user. 

## Third party links

Our Site may contain links to other sites that RepairClinic.com does not own or operate. Also, links to our Site may be found on third party websites on which we advertise. Except as provided herein, we will not provide any of your personal information to these third parties without your consent. We provide links to third party websites as a convenience to the user. These links are not intended as an endorsement of or referral to the linked websites. The linked websites have separate and independent privacy statements, notices and terms of use, which we recommend you read carefully. We do not have any control over such websites, and therefore we have no responsibility or liability for the manner in which the organizations that operate such linked websites may collect, use or disclose, secure and otherwise treat your personal information. 

## Disclosure of personal information

Except as outlined in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose, sell, rent, trade or otherwise transfer your personal information to third parties without your consent. 

**Service Provider Arrangements:** We may transfer (or otherwise make available) your personal information to our affiliates and other third parties who provide services on our behalf. For example, we may use service providers to authorize and process payments, ship our products, send email on our behalf, host our Website and operate certain of its features. 

Your personal information may be maintained and processed by our affiliates and other third party service providers in Canada, the US or other foreign jurisdictions. Our service providers are given the information they need to perform their designated functions, and we do not authorize them to use or disclose personal information for their own purposes. For information about the manner in which our service providers treat your personal information, contact us as set out below. 

**Sale of Business:** We may transfer any information we have about you as an asset in connection with a merger or sale (including transfers made as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings) involving all or part of RepairClinic.com or as part of a corporate reorganization or stock sale or other change in corporate control. 

**Legal:** RepairClinic.com, our affiliates and our Canadian, US and other service providers may provide your personal information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order, or to an investigative body in the case of a breach of an agreement or contravention of law, or as otherwise may be required or permitted by applicable Canadian, US or other law. We may also disclose personal information where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims. 

## Access to Information

Depending on the jurisdiction in which you reside, you may have the right to access, update, and correct inaccuracies in your personal information in our custody and control. You may request access, updating and corrections of inaccuracies in your personal information by contacting us as set out below. We may request certain personal information for the purposes of verifying the identity of the individual seeking access to their personal information records. 

## Contact

Please contact us with any questions and/or comments you may have. 

RepairClinic.com  
Attn: Customer Service  
48600 Michigan Avenue  
Canton, Michigan USA 48188-2240  
1-800-269-2609 (for calls within the U.S. and Canada)  
1-734-495-3079 (for calls from US Territories and APO/FPO bases)  
Fax: 1-734-495-3842  

Dated: May 2012
